

# **ABOUT ME**

My name is Mohcine 25 years old, a passionate Web Development and a with a considerable experience in the field of development and software engineering building and creating apps, Good At Coding And Quick At Learning. I started my journey in software development since 2016 and gradually managed to take my skills to the next level by consistently practicing and self-teaching myself all the necessary technologies.

#### SKILL

Computer Repairs

Computer Network installation & Repair

Development with New Technologies

Devloppment with javascript and php

React JS & Php Laravel & Bootstrap

# LANGUANGE





**English** 

Deutsch

# **HOBBIES**

Electronics Repair Swimming Gaming Chess

# MOHCINE ELHADDAD ASOUFI

IT SPECIALIST & FULL STACK DEVELOPPER

### CONTACT

- +212636948887
- contact@mohssendev.dev
- mohssenasoufi@gmail.com
- O Hay mabrouka rue 10 no 53
- www.mohssendev.dev

### **EXPERIENCE**

2020

**INFOMEDIA** 

internship

Computer and network repairs

# **FREELANCE**

2015-2019

Ecommerce

Selling online products

drop shipping affiliate marketing

2014

**VIVIANI RAIDERS** 

Caissier

2012-2014

**COMPUTER MAINTENANCE** 

**Atelier** 

Computer and Laptop, smartphone repair and troubleshooting.

install all types of operation systems

# **EDUCATION**

2021-2022 Development Digital Web full stack

Ofppt

2020-2021 Maintenance et Support

Informatique et Réseaux

Ofppt

2019 Bac Science Humain

2018 Driving License Type: B